And...
Last summer we did so, me and Amanda - my fiancee - that we went on a holiday.
A motorcycle holiday to Öland.
It is an island on the southeastern part of Sweden.
Very nice.
And then we took an old, scruffy ...
Old and risky - but big - motorcycle called Honda Deauville.
We took it there, and then we noticed that we love this.
It was as much fun to go on a motorcycle holiday together.
So then I did so I sold both Hondan and my Triumph Trident 660
and bought a Triumph Tiger 900 GT Pro.
And the idea of this Youtube channel is, among other things, to take with you on fun trips, and to great places in Sweden.
So from the motorcycle.
I'll take you on the motorcycle.
You sit something like here.
And so...
are we going.
So I hope you will look forward to it.
I also like to read books.
Especially fantasy, horror and science fiction.
I like playing video games,
And I like to watch sports.
Football, Hockey, Formula 1, Motogp ...